Guide to the Trent Harris independent film collection 1977-2007
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- Plan 10 from outer space 2 of 2 2/22/95, 1995 February 22; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 264)
- Plan 10 from outer space 89:45, 1997 June 26; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 265)
- Plan 10 from outer space KUTV news story, Undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 266)
- Plan 10 from outer space reel 1 of 2, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 267)
- Plan 10 from outer space reel 2 BGS, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 268)
- Plan 10 from outer space reel 2 of 2, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 269)
- Plan 10 from outer space 'submaster', Undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 270)
- Plan 10 from Utah reel 1 fx, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 271)
- Plan 10 KTUX lawsuit story 12/29/93, 1993 December 29; VHS videocassette (Cassette 272)
- Plan 10 parade music 1, Undated; DAT audiocassette (Cassette 273)
- Plan 10 R1 and R2 release copy, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 274)
- Plan 10 R3 music VHS copy, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 275)
- Plan 10 reel 3 BG, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 276)
- Plan 10 reel 3 mono, Undated; DAT audiocassette (Cassette 277)
- Plan 10 stereo music, Undated; DAT audiocassette (Cassette 278)
- Provo pix, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 279)
- R:E/show reel 1/pix dupe, Undated; 35mm film (Reel 280)
- Raccoon night footage, new baby footage for London Marie Lorraine Ruff (?), Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 281)
- Radio West with Doug Fabrizio Trent Harris and delightful water universe, Undated; CD (Disc 282)
- Rainbow bridge 1, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 283)
- Rainbow bridge 2, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 284)
- Ray Lampley/John Trescott in Los Angeles, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 285)
- Religion and ethics, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 286)
- Reuters Myanmar monks footage, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 287)
- Rev. Howard Finster 1, paradies garden, rev. Howard Finster in his studio, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 288)
- Romero, church of Jayne Mansfield, foxifre, seagulls, Gill Huff 1, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 289)
- Rough cut Cambodia November 2001 dub, 2001 November; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 290)
- Rough edit pieces of Beaver Trilogy with Sean Penn, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 291)
- Rubin and Ed, Undated; 35mm film (Reel 292)
- Rubin and Ed, 2 copies, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 293)
- Rubin and Ed (1 of 4), Undated; 35mm film (Reel 294)
- Rubin and Ed (1 of 5), Undated; 35mm film (Reel 295)
- Rubin and Ed (2 of 4), Undated; 35mm film (Reel 296)
- Rubin and Ed (2 of 5), Undated; 35mm film (Reel 297)
- Rubin and Ed (3 of 4), Undated; 35mm film (Reel 298)
- Rubin and Ed (3 of 5), Undated; 35mm film (Reel 299)
- Rubin and Ed (4 of 4), Undated; 35mm film (Reel 300)
- Rubin and Ed (4 of 5), Undated; 35mm film (Reel 301)
- Rubin and Ed (5 of 5), Undated; 35mm film (Reel 302)
- Rubin and Ed (parts), Undated; 35mm film (Reel 303)
- Rubin and Ed (show reel 5 pix dup), Undated; 35mm film (Reel 304)
- Rubin and Ed clips, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 305)
- Rubin and Ed KUTV Take two interview with Trent Harris, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 306)
- Rubin and Ed premiere, KTVX 3 min, KUTV 3 min, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 307)
- Rubin and Ed test, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 308)
- Rubin and Ed, running after antelope, short stories for ATC, the west desert, Tibetan monks, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 309)
- Rush-more by Trent Harris about Larry Robert's last trip, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 310)
- Rwanda footage, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 311)
- Saint Joy ascending, Undated; Betamax videocassette (Cassette 312)
- Salt Lake City cover 4 - 2006 temple, churches, U of U, courthouse, Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 313)
- Save more lambs and Farm family, 2006; 16mm film (Reel 314)
- Sean Penn Beaver Kid, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 315)
- Sean Penn Beaver Kid 2 20 min, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 316)
- Shaolin monks, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 317)
- Sierra Leone (1-5), Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 318)
- Sierra Leone 2004 (6-10), Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 319)
- Silver heads directed by Yevgeniy Yufit and Vladimir Maslov 1 hr. 23 min., Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 320)
- South Africa 1988, Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 321)
- South Africa Ndebele and Mbude 1988, VHS videocassette (Cassette 322)
- Stock - Beaver beach and misc, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 323)
- Stock footage water sports, Undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 324)
- Stock footage water sports, strange footage 1950s underwater sports, Undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 325)
- Story log - Allen Ginsberg, George Romero, Pavlo Solerie, Lief Garrett, Ed Emshwiller, Blen Bailey, seagulls/marching band, Gill Huff, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 326)
- Sumba 2/2005, 2005 February; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 327)
- Sumba 2/2005 1 tape Bali, 2005 February; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 328)
- Supplemental material (Trent Harris), 2005 February; Audiocassette (Cassette 329)
- T Leary original and mag 1, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 330)
- T Leary original and mag 4 workprint, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 331)
- T Leary sound 2, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 332)
- T Leary sound 3, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 333)
- Tanzania 2007, Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 334)
- The Barons, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 335)
- The Barons Motorcycle Gang (A-roll), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 336)
- The Barons Motorcycle Gang (B-roll), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 337)
- The Barons Motorcycle Gang (copy 1 of 2), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 338)
- The Barons Motorcycle Gang (copy 2 of 2), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 339)
- The Barons Motorcycle Gang (optical negative), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 340)
- The Beaver Kid part 1 long version, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 341)
- The Beaver Kid part 2, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 342)
- The Beaver Trilogy - interview Trent Harris This American Life NPR copy 1, Undated; CD (Disc 343)
- The cement ball of earth, heaven and hell, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 344)
- The central farming region: food for a nation, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 345)
- The end Joe Frank, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 346)
- The Englishman knew, master 19:30, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 347)
- The greatest love story ever told 22:00, 1996 May 23; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 348)
- The office of information presents Artist's models (2 copies), Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 349)
- The office of information presents Crab louse, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 350)
- The Orkly Kid director: Trent Harris, Undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 351)
- The wild goose chronicles 3 -Brazil, Undated; DVD (Disc 352)
- Theobold's big jump, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 353)
- This American Life – reruns beaver trilogy, Undated; CD (Disc 354)
- This American Life episodes 101-104, Undated; DVD (Disc 355)
- Tibet protests, San Francisco protests, Olympics 4/9/00, 2000 April 9; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 356)
- Tiger temple Thailand 2004, Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 357)
- Travel Lg 3, Woodruff Geyser 1/29/97, geyser, king of Moab, rock sculpture of Mussolini, 1997 January 29; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 358)
- Trent Harris interview - Plan 10 from outer space, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 359)
- Trent Harris interview on Take two for Rubin and Ed, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 360)
- Trent Harris: extra, dog catcher, Carl Hayden (jackpot), Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 361)
- Trent take two, 1995 March 19; VHS videocassette (Cassette 362)
- Turkmenistan, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 363)
- Turkmenistan supplemental, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 364)
- Unknown 3 (interview with senior citizen newlywed couple), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 365)
- Unknown 16mm (1 of 2) (senior citizens at dance hall), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 366)
- Unknown 16mm (2 of 2) (senior citizens at dance hall), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 367)
- Unlabeled, Undated; DVC64l videocassette (Cassette 368)
- V.O. open W.G., Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 369)
- Vernal and Subway 1977, 16mm film (Reel 370)
- Vernal and Subway A-roll, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 371)
- Vernal and Subway B-roll, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 372)
- Vernal and Subway magstocks, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 373)
- Vernal, Subway, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 374)
- Vietnam, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 375)
- VO 2, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 376)
- VO W.G. open-end Laura, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 377)
- VO W.G. wild goose voiceover, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 378)
- W.G. end - ants and sign, sniffy, Andrea pix, darn V.O., flat tire, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 379)
- W.G. pickups, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 380)
- Waits for plane, fired, Bill Brenda, rd. to Camus, Megan, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 381)
- Walter Hart Plan 10 from outer space part 1 of 1 11/30/94, 1994 November 30; DAT audiocassette (Cassette 382)
- We the people 3 min NBC, Howard Finster 6 min NBC, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 383)
- We the people 3 min, NBC, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 384)
- We the people, produced by Trent Harris, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 385)
- Wendover 2004 - Anola Gay hanger, bomb drop on Hiroshima 2004, Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 386)
- What price power, Undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 387)
- Wild goose acid 1, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 388)
- Wild goose master, Undated; DVC64l videocassette (Cassette 389)
- Wild goose master 62 min, Undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 390)
- Wild goose naked reality part 2 24 min, Undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 391)
- Wild goose yourself, Undated; DVC64l videocassette (Cassette 392)
- World in our walls 1999, VHS videocassette (Cassette 393)
- Yoyo McCarty yoko 8/14/97, 1997 August 14; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 394)
- Yoyo training, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 395)
- Yvgeny Yufits' Wooden Room – Russian experimental maker, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 396)